Guide to the Riverwalk Jazz Collection ARS.0129
Archive of Recorded Sound
- Posters, artwork, awards, realia
  - New York Festivals Finalist Awards [with correspondence], 1994, 1996; 2 items (Audio 78)
  - Promotional posters with Riverwalk logo for event display [drymounted, oversize], 7 posters (Folder-large 265, Folder-large 264)
  - Promotional conference/trade show display posters and signage, 1993-07-19; 10 items (Audio 78)
  - Radio station "on-air" light sign, 1 item (Box 90)
  - Reflections: The Happiest Jazz Band [LP-sized booklet about Cullums and Happy Jazz Band], 1972; 1 item (Audio 78)
  - Riverwalk, Live From The Landing Appreciation Day Proclamation from City of San Antonio, 1991-03-19; 1 item (Audio 78)
  - Sacramento Jazz Jubilee plaques presented to Pacific Vista Productions, 1999-2002; 3 item(s) (Audio 78)
  - Toy 1940s microphone-style AM/FM radio, 1 item (Box 90)